http://www.ulpanet.com/privacy/

Partners
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number, credit card information or Education net ltd. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To improve our website;
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To process transactions;
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To send periodic emails;
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.ulpanet.com
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on 1.1.2007
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
www.ulpanet.com
Hagolan 10
Ramat Gan, Israel 5226656
Israel
info@ulpanet.com
972777004420
This policy is powered by Trust Guard, your PCI compliance authority.
Modern HebrewBeginners course
Intermediate course
Advanced course
Biblical HebrewGenesis Stories I
Genesis Stories II
Genesis Stories III
Follow us on Facebook
Follow us on Google+
Contact us
Your Name
Your Email
Interested in:
Modern Hebrew Biblical Hebrew
Country:
---United States of America (+1)Afghanistan (+93)Albania (+355)Algeria (+213)American Samoa (+1684)Andorra (+376)Angola (+244)Anguilla (+1264)Antarctica Casey Base (+1672)Antarctica Scott Base (+1672)Antigua and Barbuda (+1268)Argentina (+54)Armenia (+374)Aruba (+297)Ascension Island (+247)Australia (+61)Austria (+43)Azerbaijan (+994)Bahamas (+1242)Bahrain (+973)Bangladesh (+880)Barbados (+1246)Belarus (+375)Belgium (+32)Belize (+501)Benin (+229)Bermuda (+1441)Bhutan (+975)Bolivia (+591)BosniaHerzegovina (+387)Botswana (+267)Brazil (+55)British Virgin Islands (+1284)Brunei (+673)Bulgaria (+359)Burkina Faso (+226)Burma (+95)Burundi (+257)Cambodia (+855)Cameroon (+237)Canada (+1)Cape Verde Island (+238)Cayman Islands (+1345)Central African Republic(+236)Chad (+235)Chile (+56)China (+86)Christmas And Cocos Islands (+672)Colombia (+57)Comoros (+269)Congo (+242)Cook Islands (+682)Costa Rica (+506)Croatia (+385)Cuba (+53)Curacao (+599)Cyprus (+357)Czech Republic (+420)Democratic Republic Of The Congo (+243)Denmark (+45)Diego Garcia (+246)Djibouti (+253)Dominica (+1767)Dominican Republic (+1809)Dominican Republic 2 (+1829)Ecuador (+593)Egypt (+20)El Salvador (+503)Equatorial Guinea (+240)Eritrea (+291)Estonia (+372)Ethiopia (+251)Faeroe Islands (+298)Falkland Islands (+500)Fiji Islands (+679)Finland (+358)France (+33)French Antilles (Martinique) (+596)French Guiana (+594)French Polynesia (+689)Gabonese Republic (+241)Gambia (+220)Georgia (+995)Germany (+49)Ghana (+233)Gibraltar (+350)Greece (+30)Greenland (+299)Grenada (+1473)Guadeloupe (+590)Guam (+1671)Guantanamo Bay (+53)Guatemala (+502)Guinea (+224)GuineaBissau (+245)Guyana (+592)Haiti (+509)Honduras (+504)Hong Kong (+852)Hungary (+36)Iceland (+354)India (+91)Indonesia (+62)Iran (+98)Iraq (+964)Ireland (+353)Israel (+972)Italy (+39)Ivory Coast (+225)Jamaica (+1876)Japan (+81)Jordan (+962)Kazakhstan (+7)Kenya (+254)Kiribati (+686)Korea, North (+850)Korea, South (+82)Kuwait (+965)Kyrgyzstan (+996)Laos (+856)Latvia (+371)Lebanon (+961)Lesotho (+266)Liberia (+231)Libya (+218)Liechtenstein (+423)Lithuania (+370)Luxembourg (+352)Macao (+853)Macedonia (+389)Madagascar (+261)Malawi (+265)Malaysia (+60)Maldives (+960)Mali (+223)Malta (+356)Marshall Islands (+692)Mauritania (+222)Mauritius (+230)Mayotte Island (+269)Mexico (Bands 13) (+52)Mexico (Bands 48) (+52)Micronesia (+691)Moldova (+373)Monaco (+377)Mongolia (+976)Montenegro (+382)Montserrat (+1664)Morocco (+212)Mozambique (+258)Myanmar (+95)Namibia (+264)Nauru (+674)Nepal (+977)Netherlands (+31)Netherlands Antilles (+599)New Caledonia (+687)New Zealand (+64)Nicaragua (+505)Niger (+227)Nigeria (+234)Niue (+683)Norfolk Island (+672)Northern Marianas Islands (+1670)Norway (+47)Oman (+968)Pakistan (+92)Palau (+680)Palestinian National Authority (+970)Panama (+507)Papua New Guinea (+675)Paraguay (+595)Peru (+51)Philippines (+63)Poland (+48)Portugal (+351)Puerto Rico 1 (+1787)Puerto Rico 2 (+1939)Qatar (+974)Reunion Island (+262)Romania (+40)Russia (+7)Rwanda (+250)San Marino (+378)Sao Tome (+239)Saudi Arabia (+966)Senegal (+221)Serbia (+381)Seychelles (+248)Sierra Leone (+232)Singapore (+65)Slovakia (+421)Slovenia (+386)Solomon Islands (+677)Somalia (+252)South Africa (+27)Spain (+34)Sri Lanka (+94)St. Eustatius (+599)St. Helena (+290)St. Kitts and Nevis (+1869)St. Lucia (+1758)St. Maarten (+599)St. Pierre and Miguelon (+508)St. Vincent (+1809)Sudan (+249)Suriname (+597)Swaziland (+268)Sweden (+46)Switzerland (+41)Syria (+963)Taiwan (+886)Tajikistan (+992)Tanzania (+255)Thailand (+66)Togo (+228)Tonga Islands (+676)Trinidad and Tobago (+1868)Tunisia (+216)Turkey (+90)Turkmenistan (+993)Turks and Caicos (+1649)Tuvalu (+688)U.S. Virgin Islands (+1340)Uganda (+256)Ukraine (+380)United Arab Emirates (+971)United Kingdom (+44)United States of America (+1)Uruguay (+598)Uzbekistan Tashkent (+998)Vanuatu (+678)Vatican City (+39)Venezuela (+58)Vietnam (+84)Wallis And Futuna Islands (+681)Western Samoa (+685)Yemen (+967)Zambia (+260)Zimbabwe (+263)
Phone
Online Hebrew Course
View our Privacy Policy.
